Contact

libetg3@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/liz-gilbert-83b9959 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Hospitals Epic Systems

Certifications

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

Liz Gilbert

RN, BSN, CMSRN at Providence St Vincent Medical Center Portland, Oregon Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the religious institutions industry. Skilled in Nonprofit Organizations, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Orthopedics, and Program Development. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from Loyola University of Chicago.

Experience

Providence St Vincent Medical Center RN
June 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months)
Portland, Oregon

Providence Health & Services RN, BSN, CMSRN May 2013 - June 2016 (3 years 2 months)

Cross Country TravCorps
Travel RN
January 2013 - May 2013 (5 months)
portland, oregon area

OHSU

RN, Trauma, Emergency General Services, Orthopedics December 2010 - January 2013 (2 years 2 months)

Rush University Medical Center RN, BSN May 2008 - January 2010 (1 year 9 months)

National Restaurant Association Assistant Manager, Registration, and Guest Services October 2003 - May 2007 (3 years 8 months) SCORE! Educational Centers Advantage Program Director July 2002 - October 2003 (1 year 4 months)

Education

Loyola University of Chicago BSN, Accelerated program · (2007 - 2008)

Indiana University Bloomington
Bachelor of Science (BS), Tourism and Business, Travel Services Marketing
Operations, · (1998 - 2002)

American College of Dublin